<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Starbucks</string>

    <string name="facebook_app_id">755740902615806</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb1234</string>
    <string name="facebook_client_token">8d86d868e4bcc1a1ae261a9caefc6b34</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string-array name="recentTransaction_orderName">
        <item name="order1">Cheesecake Milkshake Frappucino Cream Starbucks</item>
        <item name="order2">Coffee Latte Macchiato Pumpkin Spice Starbucks</item>
        <item name="order3">Caramel Macchiato</item>
        <item name="order4">Matcha Green Tea Latte</item>
        <item name="order5">Pink Drink</item>
        <item name="order6">Iced White Chocolate Mocha</item>
        <item name="order7">Nitro Cold Brew with Sweet Cream</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="recentTransaction_orderDate">
        <item name="date1">Today, 17:45 PM</item>
        <item name="date2">Oct 14th 2021</item>
        <item name="date3">Dec 31st 2022</item>
        <item name="date4">Apr 18th 2024</item>
        <item name="date5">Jul 7th 2023</item>
        <item name="date6">Nov 23rd 2023</item>
        <item name="date7">Feb 14th 2024</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="recentTransaction_orderPrice">
        <item name="price1">-$19.65</item>
        <item name="price2">-$18.75</item>
        <item name="price3">-$8.37</item>
        <item name="price4">-$13.99</item>
        <item name="price5">-$27.50</item>
        <item name="price6">-$4.83</item>
        <item name="price7">-$16.75</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="today_type">
        <item name="type1">Payment</item>
        <item name="type2">Reward</item>
        <item name="type3">Payment</item>
        <item name="type4">Reward</item>
        <item name="type5">Payment</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="today_date">
        <item name="date1">10.28.2021</item>
        <item name="date2">9.28.2021</item>
        <item name="date3">8.27.2021</item>
        <item name="date4">7.26.2021</item>
        <item name="date5">6.26.2021</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="today_cost">
        <item name="cost1">-$19.65</item>
        <item name="cost2">-$00.00</item>
        <item name="cost3">-$11.35</item>
        <item name="cost4">-$00.00</item>
        <item name="cost5">-$4.50</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="today_reward">
        <item name="reward1">+5 ⭐️</item>
        <item name="reward2">-12 ⭐</item>
        <item name="reward1">+10 ⭐️</item>
        <item name="reward2">-15 ⭐</item>
        <item name="reward1">+15 ⭐️</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="yestd_type">
        <item name="type1">Payment</item>
        <item name="type2">Payment</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="yestd_date">
        <item name="date1">04.09.2023</item>
        <item name="date2">04.09.2023</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="yestd_cost">
        <item name="cost1">-$19.65</item>
        <item name="cost2">-$4.50</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="yestd_reward">
        <item name="reward1">+5 ⭐️</item>
        <item name="reward2">+12 ⭐</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="prev7Days_type">
        <item name="type1">Payment</item>
        <item name="type2">Reward</item>
        <item name="type3">Payment</item>
        <item name="type4">Reward</item>
        <item name="type5">Payment</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="prev7Days_date">
        <item name="date1">10.28.2021</item>
        <item name="date2">9.28.2021</item>
        <item name="date3">8.27.2021</item>
        <item name="date4">7.26.2021</item>
        <item name="date5">6.26.2021</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="prev7Days_cost">
        <item name="cost1">-$19.65</item>
        <item name="cost2">-$00.00</item>
        <item name="cost3">-$11.35</item>
        <item name="cost4">-$00.00</item>
        <item name="cost5">-$4.50</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="prev7Days_reward">
        <item name="reward1">+5 ⭐️</item>
        <item name="reward2">-12 ⭐</item>
        <item name="reward1">+10 ⭐️</item>
        <item name="reward2">-15 ⭐</item>
        <item name="reward1">+15 ⭐️</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="forYou_caption">
        <item name="caption1">Art in a Cup: Buy One Get One</item>
        <item name="caption2">12th Dec 2021: Pistachio Christmas Tree Frapuccino</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="news_caption">
        <item name="caption1">Elevate Your Tea Experience with New Starbucks Teavana Beverages!</item>
        <item name="caption2">Shop Now: BTS X Starbucks Korea: Limited Edition Menus &amp; Merchanidise In A Pretty Purple Shade</item>
        <item name="caption3">Share the Holiday Spirit with Starbucks</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="copyright">© 2023 Starbucks Coffee Company. All rights reserved.</string>
    <string name="birthday_text">Let us know your birthday so you won\'t miss a birthday treat</string>

    <string name="registerStarbucksCard">To register your Starbucks Card, simply log in to your\nStarbucks Singapore account on the memberships portal\nonline here or our Starbucks Singapore mobile app to add\n(+) it in. If you do not have an account, you may create an\naccount here.</string>
    <string name="registerEmailAddress">If you have any issues in changing your email address,\ndo fill up the form here and share your new and old\nemail address with us. Our team will get back to you within 5 working days.</string>
    <string name="changeAccPassword1">To reset your password, click on the "Forget Password?" button found on the login page here and a reset password link with instructions will be sent to your registered email address.</string>
    <string name="changeAccPassword2">If you have any issues in changing your password, do fill up the form here. Our team will get back to you within 5 working days. If you do not receive the email within the next few minutes, please check your email account\'s Junk/Spam folder</string>
    <string name="passwordCondition1">Have 9 or more characters</string>
    <string name="passwordCondition2">Contain alphabet and numeric characters</string>
    <string name="passwordCondition3">Contain at least 1 special character(eg, !, @, #, $, %, ^)</string>

    <string name="FAQ14">I have selected the wrong birthday month during the activation of my card, how can i change it?</string>
    <string name="wrongBDMonth">Customers are not allowed to make changes to their birthday month on their account. If you\'re looking to change it, do fill up the form here and share your birth month with us, we will assist you accordingly</string>


    <string name="FAQ15">How does starbucks protect my privacy after I register my starbucks Card?</string>
    <string name="cardPrivacy">Starbucks does not sell or share your personal information,\nincluding your name, address, phone number, email\naddress, birth date, financial information etc. With\nthird parties. We take great care in managing your personal\ninformation only in accordance with our Starbucks Privacy\nStatement</string>

    <string name="FAQ16">What methods of payment can be used to activate or reload a Starbucks Card?</string>
    <string name="ReloadStarbucksCard">Cash, Nets or credit card can be used to activate and/or reload a Starbucks Card.</string>

    <string name="FAQ17">Can a Starbucks Card be used to activate or reload another Starbucks Card?</string>
    <string name="StarbucksCardReloadCard">No. Only cash, Nets or credit card can be used to activate\nand/or reload a starbucks Card. However, you can log in to\nyour My Starbucks Card account online at\nwww.starbucks.com.sg or via the Starbucks mobile apps to\ntransfer funds between any of your registered Starbucks Cards.</string>

    <string name="FAQ18">What is the minimum activation amount?</string>
    <string name="MinimumActivationAmount">S$10 is the minimum activation amount.</string>

    <string name="FAQ19">What is the maximum activation amount?</string>
    <string name="MaxActAmount">S$300 is the maximum activation amount.</string>

    <string name="FAQ20">Where can I use my Starbucks Card?</string>
    <string name="WhereToUseCard">Your starbucks Card can be used at all Starbucks stores in\nSingapore except stores located at Changi Airport\n(excluding Jewel).</string>

    <string name="FAQ21">How do I view and manage my Starbucks Card account?</string>
    <string name="viewAndManageCard">You can check your Starbucks Card account details,\ntransactions, Stars balance and Rewards as well as reload\nyour card by logging into your account through our website\nhere or through our Starbucks Singapore mobile apps</string>

    <string name="FAQ22">Will my receipt have my Starbucks Card\nbalance on it when I use it to make a\npurchase?</string>
    <string name="cardReceipt">Yes.</string>

    <string name="FAQ23">Does Starbucks charge any service fee for my Starbucks Card?</string>
    <string name="cardServiceFee">No.</string>

    <string name="FAQ24">How do I reload my Starbucks Card</string>
    <string name="reloadStarbucksCard">You can reload your Starbucks Card at any participating\nStarbucks store in Singapore or through our the Starbucks Singapore mobile application. You can reload a minimum of S$10 each time(i.e. you can only reload in\ndenominations of S$10 per load). The maximum balance\nthat can be stored on a Starbucks Card at any time id S$300.</string>

    <string name="FAQ25">Can I use my Starbucks Card when i travel internationally?</string>
    <string name="travelCard">No. Singapore Starbucks Cards cannot be used in any other\nmarkets. The cards can only be used in Singapore.</string>

    <string name="FAQ26">What should I do if my Starbucks Card is lost or stolen?</string>
    <string name="stolenCard">If you have registered your Starbucks Card or have added it\nto an existing account, please log into your account through\nthe member\'s portal, click "My Cards", and select the Card\nyou would like to report lost. Click on "Report Lost Card"\nand follow the instructions given to transfer the balance of your lost Card to another existing Card or request for a\nreplacement card. Alternatively, you may also report lost of\nyour Starbucks Card via the\n\nStarbucks Singapore App under the "Manage" section\nof your Starbucks Card.\n\nIf you have not registered your Starbucks Card, please\nregister if before using it to make purchases in order to\nearn Stars and collect Rewards on all your purchases. If you are unable to register, do reach out the customer care\nteam for further assistance.</string>

    <string name="FAQ27">Can the Starbucks Card be refunded?</string>
    <string name="refundCard">Refunds can only be done personally at the Starbucks head\n office in Singapore and in accordance with the refund\npolicy and procedures in the Starbucks Card Terms of Use.\nYou must present the original sale receipt for the purchase\nof the Starbucks Card together with the card for a refund to be processed.</string>

    <string name="FAQ28">How do I check the remaining value on my Starbucks Card?</string>
    <string name="remainingValue">You can log into your Starbucks Card account via our\nStarbucks Card membership portal or through our\nStarbucks Singapore mobile apps. You can also reload your\ncard through our website or our Starbucks Singapore\nmobile apps.</string>

    <string name="FAQ29">Can I view my transaction history and Stars earned?</string>
    <string name="transactionHistoryStars">You can view your transaction history and the Stars earned\nby logging into your Starbucks Card account through our\nwebsite here(up to past 6 months) or through our Starbucks Singapore mobile app (up to first 10 transaction\nof the past 3 months). Please allow up to 24 hours for\ndetails of the transaction history to be updated to your\naccount.</string>

    <string name="FAQ30">Can I use my Starbucks Card when i travel internationally?</string>
    <string name="rewardList">You can view your rewards by logging into your Starbucks\nCard account through our website at\nwww.starbucks.com.sg or through our Starbucks Singapore mobile app.</string>

    <string name="FAQ31">Can I use my Starbucks Card when i travel internationally?</string>
    <string name="transferFundBetweenCards">You can transfer funds between your registered cards by\nlogging into your Starbucks Card account through our\nwebsite at www.starbucks.com.sg or through our Starbucks\nSingapore mobile apps.</string>

    <!-- For Starbucks Reward FAQ-->
    <string name="FAQ32">What is Starbucks Reward program</string>
    <string name="starbucksRewardProgram">Starbucks Rewards is a membership program that rewards and thanks loyal customers for patronizing Starbucks stores in Singapore. The program benefits all Starbucks Rewards members as you earn Stars when you pay via your registered Starbucks Card at all participating Starbucks stores in Singapore, amongst other rewards. Additionally, if you sign up to receive communications from Starbucks when you register your Card, you will be among the first to receive news, exclusive offers and information about Starbucks.</string>

    <string name="FAQ33">How does Starbucks Rewards program work?</string>
    <string name="starbucksRewardProgramWork1">You can join the program by registering your Starbucks Card via http://www.starbucks.com.sg/rewards/join. Simply purchase a Starbucks Card in any of our stores (except for stores located at Changi Airport other than Starbucks Jewel Changi Airport) by loading a minimum of S$10. Alternatively, if you do not have a Starbucks Card, you can sign up with a digital card via https://www.starbucks.com.sg/rewards/join or the Starbucks Singapore app. You can start collecting Stars and earning rewards by paying with your registered Starbucks Card. For every S$1 you spend, you will earn 1 Star. There are two membership levels in this program.</string>
    <string name="starbucksRewardProgramWork2">Upon creating a new Starbucks account when you register your first Starbucks Card, you will automatically become a Green level Starbucks Rewards member. This means you will receive the following privileges:</string>
    <string name="starbucksRewardProgramWork3">After you earn 300 Stars within a period of 12 months, you will be upgraded to a Gold level Starbucks Reward member, where you will receive these additional privileges (on top of what\'s mentioned above):</string>
    <string name="starbucksRewardProgramWork4">^Applicable to newly upgraded Gold members only, Gold members will receive one Gold Card in his or her lifetime.</string>

    <string name="FAQ34">How do I upgrade to Gold level?</string>
    <string name="upgradeGoldLevel">Once you qualify for Green level, you will be at that level for a full year from the date you qualified - this will be your anniversary date to earn 300 Stars in order to upgrade to Gold level. Stars are refreshed and reset every year and will not be brought forward</string>

    <string name="FAQ35">How do I maintain Gold Level status?</string>
    <string name="maintainGoldLevelStatus">Once you qualify for Green level, you will be at that level for a full year from the date you qualified - this will be your anniversary date to earn 300 Stars in order to extend your Gold level membership for another year.\n\nIf you do not earn 300 Stars in one year, you will start your new year at Green level. Stars are refreshed and reset every year and will not be brought forward.</string>

    <string name="FAQ36">What are the participating Starbucks stores for the Starbucks stores for the Starbucks stores for the Starbucks Rewards program?</string>
    <string name="participatingRewardProgram">Starbucks Rewards are enjoyed with spend on your registered Starbucks Card. You can make payment for your Starbucks purchase at all stores in Singapore except stores that are located at Singapore Changi Airport, other than Starbucks Jewel Changi Airport. This program stated here is applicable in Singapore only.</string>

    <string name="FAQ37">How do I register for a Starbucks Rewards account if I\'m not a member?</string>
    <string name="RegisterAccIfNotMember">Registering for Starbucks Rewards is easy. You can join the program by registering your Starbucks Card. Simply purchase a Starbucks Card in any of our stores (except for stores located at Changi Airport other than Starbucks Jewel Changi Airport) by loading a minimum of S$10</string>
    <string name="RegisterAccIfNotMember2">Alternatively, you can join by creating an account via the Starbucks Singapore app or here.\nUpon successful registration, you can start collecting Stars and earning Rewards by paying with your registered Starbucks Card.</string>

    <string name="FAQ38">Can I qualify for multiple renewals in a single year? For example, if I earn 600 Stars in one year, will I be in the Gold Level for the next two years?</string>
    <string name="multipleRenewalInOneYear1">No. Every year on your anniversary date(te date you qualified for that level), we will track if you have earned the minimum number of Stars required for that membership level.</string>
    <string name="multipleRenewalInOneYear2">For example, if you are a Gold member, we will track to see if you have earned a minimum of 300 Stars during the 12-month period before your anniversary date. if so, you will remain at the Gold level for another year. Your Star balance will still revert to zero and Stars will not be brought forward.</string>

    <string name="FAQ39">What are Stars and how do I earn them?</string>
    <string name="WhatAreStars">You can earn Stars and receive rewards simply by paying with any Starbucks Card registered to your account at a participating Starbucks store in Singapore(except stores located at Changi Airport other than Starbucks Jewel Changi Airport). For every S$1 you spend, you will earn 1 Star. For example, if you have spent S10.10, you will see 10.10 Stars reflected in your account for that transaction. Do note that Stars may take up to 24 hours to be reflected in your account.</string>

    <string name="FAQ40">How are the Stars used?</string>
    <string name="HowStarsUsed">The Stars are used to determine the level of Starbucks-Rewards membership and rewards that are eligible for redemption.</string>

    <string name="FAQ41">What rewards can I redeem my Stars for?</string>
    <string name="RewardsToRedeemWithStars">Not applicable on bottled beverages, seasonal promotional items (such as Mooncake Boxes) and purchases or reloading of Starbucks Card.</string>
    <string name="RewardsToRedeemWithStars2">$20 off a single transaction OR 3 complimentary Grande size handcrafted drinks in a single transaction with every 160 Stars $20 off a single transactions is not applicable on seasonal promotional items (such as Mooncake Boxes) and purchase or reloading of Starbucks Card.</string>

    <string name="FAQ42">What drinks can I redeem with my Stars?</string>
    <string name="drinksICanRedeem">You can redeem any Grande-sized handcrafted drink of your choice (except bottled drinks and coffee traveller) at all a[rticipating Starbucks Singapore store(except stores located at Changi Airport other than Starbucks Jewel Changi Airport). All drink customizations(adding of syrup, espresso shots, drizzles, java chips and change of milk options) are complimentary with this redemption.</string>

    <string name="FAQ43">What is a Star and how do I earn one?</string>
    <string name="whatIsStar">You will earn Stars and receive rewards simply by paying with any Starbucks Card registered to your account at a participating Starbucks store in Singapore. For every S$1 you spend, you will earn 1 Star. Earning of Stars is attained only through purchases in-store and does not include loading on monetary values into Starbucks Card(s)</string>

    <string name="FAQ44">Do my Stars expire?</string>
    <string name="doStarsExpire">Yes. Stars will expire 1 year from your anniversary date(the date you qualified for the current level of your Starbucks Rewards membership). After registering a new account, you have 12 months to earn Stars to reach the next level. Upon reaching a new level, you will have another 12 months from the date that you reached that level to earn Stars to maintain your membership at that level or to progress to the next level.</string>
    <string name="doStarsExpire2">This means that if you have just created a new account, you  have one year to earn 300 Stars to reach Gold level.</string>
    <string name="doStarsExpire3">Once you hit Gold level, you will have one year from that date(your anniversary date) to earn 300 Stars to maintain your Gold level. If you earn less than 300 Stars, you\'ll start the new year as a Green level member. Stars get refreshed annually and you will not be brought forward.</string>

    <!--Mobile Order and Pay-->
    <string name="FAQ45">What is Mobile Order &amp; Pay?</string>
    <string name="whatIsMOP">Mobile Order &amp; Pay is a feature on the Starbucks Singapore mobile app, it is a stramlined store experience for Starbucks Rewards members who order and pay with out app. Place an order, pay ahead, and choose a pickup method that best suits you - Order &amp; PickUp Now | Schedule An Order | Dine-in Ordering With Mobile Order &amp; Pay, you can collect Stars and earn Rewards with Starbucks rewards just like you do when paying  in store.\n\nStarbucks Singapore mobile app is available for download on the Ap Store and Google Play Store.</string>

    <string name="FAQ46">Where is Mobile Order &amp; Pay available?</string>
    <string name="whereMOP">Mobile Order &amp; Pay is available at all Starbucks Singapore stores except: Samsung Hub, Sentosa(Imbiah Lookout), Universal Studios Singapore, and all Changi Airport stores including Jewel.</string>

    <string name="FAQ47">Why can\'t I update the Starbucks Singapore app to the latest version on my phone?</string>
    <string name="updateStarbucksApp">If you are an existing user of the Starbucks Singapore mobile app and the app does not automatically update to the latest version, simply uninstall the exiting app, and download the latest version from the App Store or Google Play Store to discover the new features.</string>

    <string name="FAQ48">How do I register for a Starbucks Rewards account if I\'m not already a member</string>
    <string name="registerIfNotMember">Registering for Starbucks Rewards is easy. You can join the program by registering via our website or out mobile app. Simply create an account and start collecting Stars and Rewards by paying with your digital Starbucks Card on your mobile app.</string>

    <string name="FAQ49">What can I purchase on Mobile Order &amp; Pay</string>
    <string name="whatICanPurchase">Almost all your favourite Starbucks beverages, food items and selected At-Home coffee &amp; tea are avilable through Mobile Order &amp; Pay. The "Order" section of the app has a menu which lists all available offerings at participating stores. With a few taps on you phone, you can customize your favourite beverages and choose to have your food served warm, just as you can with in-store orders.</string>

    <string name="FAQ50">How do I place an Order</string>
    <string name="howToPlaceOrder">To use Mobile Order and Pay, tap on the "Order" option located on the bottom of the screen. You can place a Mobile Order in three ways:</string>
    <string name="howToPlaceOrder2">Place an order and pay ahead using the app. This allows you to walk in without queueing a line and pick up your freshly made order at the pickup area, all within minutes.</string>
    <string name="howToPlaceOrder3">Place an order, pay ahead using the app and schedule a pickup time that\'s most convenient for you. Then, swing by our store to pick up your freshly made order at the choseen time.</string>
    <string name="howToPlaceOrder4">Once you have found a table in-store, place an order, pay ahead on the app and we will notify you when your order is ready. That means you can skip the queue and pick up your freshly made order at the counter when it is ready.\n\nAll dine-in orders will be served in for-here serverware. Find out how to order ahead here.</string>

    <string name="FAQ51">How do I pick up my order?</string>
    <string name="howToPickUpOrder">When your order is ready for pick-up, you wil receive a notification message sent via the Starbucks Singapore mobile app. Please proceed to the store you have selected within the estimated "ready by" time shown on the app or the "scheduled time" if you have chosen Schedule an Order.\n\nCollect your order at the pick-up area by presenting your order details to our baristas.</string>

    <string name="FAQ52">How do I choose which store to place my order at?</string>
    <string name="chooseWhichStore">When you use Mobile Order &amp; Pay, the app will detect the nearest participating Starbucks store to your current location. The app will also display the current menu availability from that store. You can either pick the store detected, or manually pick another store by tapping the map or using the "Search" function. Once your order is submitted, you will be able to change the pick-up store.</string>

    <string name="FAQ53">Can I place an order before a store is open?</string>
    <string name="beforeStoreOpens">Mobile Orders can only be made within the store operating hours.</string>

    <string name="FAQ54">Is there a maximum number of items that can be ordered through Mobile Order &amp; Pay?</string>
    <string name="maxNumberOfItems">You can order a maximum of 15 items.</string>

    <string name="FAQ55">How long will my order take, when placed through Mobile Order &amp; Pay?</string>
    <string name="howLongWillOrderTake">Before you place your order, an estimated prep time absed on the store chosen will be displayed, Once you have checked our and submitted your order, you will be given an estimated "ready by" time. If you hae chosen Schedule an Order, simply arrive at the scheduled time.\n\nWaiting time varies according to the store chosen and time of day. Once your order is ready for pick-up, you will receive a notification message via the Starbucks Singapore mobile app.</string>

    <string name="FAQ56">Can I schedule the pick-up tme for my Mobile Order?</string>
    <string name="schedulePickUpTime">This is only available when you pick thr Schedule an Order option.\n\nSimply pick a store, schedule your order at a pickup time of your choice. The earliest time slot you can schedule an order is 1 hour from the ordering time, with an interval of 15 minutes, up to 15 minutes prior to store closing</string>

    <string name="FAQ57">How many days in advance can I schedule my Mobile Order?</string>
    <string name="scheduleAdvance">You can schedule your order within a day. The earliest time slot you can schedule an order is 1 hour from the ordering time, ith an interval of 15 minutes prior to store closing.</string>

    <!--Starbucks online store-->
    <string name="FAQ58">As a Starbucks Rewards member, do I earn Starts &amp; Rewards on all my purchases in Starbucks Online Store?</string>
    <string name="earnRewardOnline">Yes. Stars &amp; Rewards will be awarded when you place your order logged in as a Starbucks Rewards member> Stars will be credited upon confirmation of order received and may take up to 24 hours to be reflected on yor account. Stars issuance does not apply to purchase of Starbucks Card eGift and Shipping Fee.</string>

    <string name="FAQ59">I have just joined as a Starbucks Rewards member. Will I be able to earn Stars on my past purchases as a guest.</string>
    <string name="earnStarsAsGuest">No, customers must log in and cart out as a member to receive Stars. If a customer carts out as a guest. he/she is unable to earn Stars on their purchases.</string>

    <string name="FAQ60">Can I redeem my Starbucks rewards member. Will I be able to earn Stars on my past purchases as a guest?</string>
    <string name="redeemRewardOnline">From time-to-time, we may run exclusive Starbucks Rewards promotions on Starbucks Online Store. For Gold members, you may also redeem 160 Stars for $20 off your online purchase. Please note that other Stars or Rewards benefits do not apply.</string>

    <string name="FAQ61">I have placed my order as a Starbucks Rewards member but forgot to redeem my Stars, apply Rewards or promo code, what should I do?</string>
    <string name="forgotApplyReward">Unfortunately, any promotions or rewards cannot be applied to an order once it is placed. We will not be able to reimburse you, but you can always save it for the next purchase with us.</string>

    <string name="FAQ62">Do I receive a Free Drink voucher when I purchase a tumbler on Starbucks Online Store</string>
    <string name="freeDrinksWhenBuyTumbler">Yes, you will receive a Free Drink voucher upon purchase of a regular-priced tumbler if you place your oder, logged in as a Starbucks Rewards member. Free Drink voucher will only be credited to your Starbucks Rewards account when the order is fulfilled and member clicks on "Order Received", or after 15 working days where we will automatically confirm the order if no response is received. This is only applicable on full-priced tumblers and does not apply on mugs, water bottles and marked down or discounted tumblers.</string>

    <string name="FAQ63">How do I check my Order Status, Purchase History and Stars Earned?</string>
    <string name="checkOrderStatus">You will be notified of your Order Status and Purchase History via your email. You may also log in to the Starbucks Rewards Member Portal and refer to the "History" tab for your Stars Earned. If you have the Starbucks Singapore app, you may view them under "Transaction History" too.</string>

    <string name="FAQ64">I have not gotten any Stars after receiving my order, how long does iI have not gotten any Stars after rt take for the Stars to be credited?</string>
    <string name="haveNotGottenStars">Upon receiving your order, please proceed to click on "Order Received" on the email sent when your order is delivered. Once we get your acknowledgement of your order received, your Stars will be automatically credited into your account within 24 hours.</string>

    <string name="FAQ65">Do I need to be a member to shop at Starbucks Online Store</string>
    <string name="memberToShopOnline">If you placed your order as a Starbucks Rewards member, you will be able to earn Stars and Rewards on the Starbucks Online Store. Beside that, having a Starbucks Rewards account will help to speed up the checkout process and allow you to do a guest checkout. However, you information and transaction record will not be stored if you opt for guest checkout.</string>

    <string name="FAQ66">What are the payment modes available on Starbucks Online Store?</string>
    <string name="paymentModesOnline">We accept VISA Credit/Debit card, Mastercard Credit/Debit card, Apple Pay, Google Pay and starbucks Card payment on the Starbucks Online store. If you are a Starbucks Rewards member, you may use your registered Starbucks Card to make payment for merchandise and Drinks &amp; Food eGift purchases. For Starbucks Card eGift purchases, you will need to pay using other payment methods.</string>

    <string name="FAQ67">Can I use multiple payment modes on a single order?</string>
    <string name="multiplePaymentModes">No, please select your preferred payment mode upon checkout. However, if your consists of a Starbucks Card eGift, you will only be able to ay using other payment mode, except your registered Starbucks Card.</string>

    <string name="FAQ68">Is there a minimum or maximum spend per order on the Starbucks Online Store?</string>
    <string name="minMaxOrder">There is no minimum spend required on the Starbucks Online Store. However, if you place your oder logged in as a Starbucks Rewards member, you are required to pay with your registered Starbucks Card which at any given time can only store a maximum balance of S$300.</string>

    <string name="FAQ69">What are the delivery options and charges?</string>
    <string name="deliveryOptionsCharges">There are two delivery options that you can choose from - Standard and Express. The charges for the delivery options are $4 and $6 respectively.</string>

    <string name="FAQ70">How long does it takes for my order to be delivered?</string>
    <string name="orderDeliveryDuration">With Express shipping, you will receive your order the next working day if orders are placed before 3pm(Mon-Fri, excludes public holidays). Standard shipping will take around 3 working days. However, do note that we do not deliver on weekends and public holidays.</string>

    <!--Starbucks Delivers-->
    <string name="FAQ71">How do I place a Starbucks Delivers(in-app delivery) order?</string>
    <string name="starbucksDeliveryOrder">You can download our Starbucks Singapore mobile app and place your order with the following steps:</string>
    <string name="starbucksDeliveryOrder2">A minimum order of $15 excluding delivery fee, will be required for all delivery orders.</string>

    <string name="FAQ72">Can I select my preferred store location for the delivery order?</string>
    <string name="selectLocation">No, you will not be able to choose your preferred store location. The nearest available store will be assigned to your order after you have entered your delivery address.</string>

    <string name="FAQ73">Can I schedule my delivery time on Starbucks Delivers?</string>
    <string name="scheduleDeliveryTime">No. We are not able to schedule any order in advance. Orders will be processed as soon as we receive them.</string>

    <string name="FAQ74">Do I need to be a Starbucks Rewards member to order via Starbucks Delivers?</string>
    <string name="doINeedToBeAMember">yes. You will have to log in as a Starbucks Rewards member via the Starbucks Singapore mobile app. As a member, you can earn Stars when you order via Starbucks Delivers.</string>

    <string name="FAQ75">What is the minimum order for delivery?</string>
    <string name="minOrderDelivery">A minimum order of $15 applies. This excludes delivery fee.</string>

    <string name="FAQ76">How much is the delivery fees?</string>
    <string name="deliveryFee">A delivery fee of $4.50 applies for each order. Do note Stars issuance for Starbucks Rewards is not applicable on delivery fees.</string>

    <string name="FAQ77">What payment mode(s) do you accept?</string>
    <string name="paymentModesDelivery">We only accept payment through your registered Starbucks Card in your account via the Starbucks Singapore mobile app where you have place your order from.</string>

    <string name="FAQ78">Can I use multiple registered Starbucks Card payment in a single order?</string>
    <string name="multiplePaymentDelivery">Only one registered Starbucks Card can be used as payment mode for a single order. Do ensure that your card balance is sufficient fpr a more seamless checkout process.</string>

    <string name="FAQ79">Does Starbucks Delivers accept cash-on-delivery?</string>
    <string name="cashOnDelivery">No, we do not accept cash-on-delivery. Only Starbucks Card is accepted as payment mode for Starbucks Delivers Order.</string>

    <string name="FAQ80">I have changed my mind, can I cancel my order?</string>
    <string name="cancelledOrder">Does Starbucks Delivers accept cash-on-delivery?</string>

    <string name="FAQ81">Can I amend my order after I have placed my order?</string>
    <string name="amendOrders">Once the order has been placed, it will be processed instantly, and allow any changes or modifications to your order will not be allowed.</string>

    <string name="FAQ82">Why is my order being cancelled?</string>
    <string name="orderCancelled">Your order may be cancelled if one of the items ordered is out of stock or it takes longer than usual to find a driver. You will receive a notification via the app, refund will be automatically processed and returned to your Starbucks Card within 1 working day. If you would like to order again, please select other items and try again.</string>

    <string name="FAQ83">Can I get a refund if my order is cancelled on Starbucks Delivers?</string>
    <string name="refundIfOrderCancelled">The options to cancel an order will only appear when the system is unable to find a driver for your order. Once the order has been cancelled, refund will be automatically processed and returned to your Starbucks Card within 1 working day.</string>

</resources>

